let questions=[
    {question:"What is Captain America's Catchphrase, which shows up starting in Captain America and is lampshaded in Avengers: Endgame?",a:"Let's get American.",b:"United States of Smash!",c:"I can do this all day.",d:"I'm here!",correct:"c",answer:"I can do this all day."},
    {question:"Thor is a member of what mythical pantheon?",a:"Norse",b:"Greek",c:"Egyptian",d:"Mayan",correct:"a",answer:"Norse"},
    {question:"Who is the first MCU villain to be a main villain for two films?",a:"Loki",b:"Thanos",c:"Obidiah Stane",d:"Green Goblin",correct:"a",answer:"Loki"},
    {question:"Who is the most recent member of the Avengers, as of November 2021?",a:"Sersi",b:"Shang Chi",c:"Loki",d:"Spiderman",correct:"b",answer:"Shang Chi"},
    {question:"Who is the main antagonist of the second Avengers film?",a:"Hydra",b:"Thanos",c:"Ultron",d:"Loki",correct:"c",answer:"Ultron"},
    {question:"What is the first film to be part of the MCU",a:"Iron Man",b:"The Incredible Hulk",c:"Thor",d:"Spiderman (2002)",correct:"a",answer:"Iron Man"},
    {question:"Besides Steve Rogers, who is the first Avenger to become a superhero",a:"Hulk",b:"Iron Man",c:"T'challa",d:"Captain Marvel",correct:"d",answer:"Captain Marvel"},
    {question:"What is the highest rated MCU Movie on Rotten Tomatoes",a:"Captain America: The Winter Soldier",b:"Spider-Man: Homecoming",c:"Avengers: Infinity War",d:"Black Panther",correct:"d",answer:"Black Panther"},
    {question:"Which of these Guardians of the Galaxy songs does not play during a fight scene?",a:"Southern Nights",b:"Come and Get Your Love",c:"Mr. Blue Sky",d:"Come a Little Bit Closer",correct:"b",answer:"Come and Get Your Love"},
    {question:"How many futures does Dr. Strange forsee in Avengers: Infinity War?",a:"10,500,602",b:"14,000,605",c:"100,000",d:"9,999,999,999",correct:"b",answer:"14,000,605"},
];